Piyush Anand

Java & Full- Stack Developer

Proactive and personable job seeker currently pursuing B.Tech in ECE from Bharati Vidyapeeth's College of Engineering in Paschim Vihar, New Delhi. Excellent written and oral communication skills. I am passionate about building excellent software that improves the lives of those around me. I believe my enthusiasm and specialized experience would make me an asset to your team.

\bowtie	piyushanand.1221@gmail.com
	9999848631
0	NEW Delhi, India
	bit.ly/piyushanand
in	linkedin.com/in/creatorpiyush
y	twitter.com/1221Piyush
0	github.com/creatorpiyush

EDUCATION

B. Tech

Bharati Vidyapeeth's College of Engineering, New Delhi

08/2018 - Present

CGPA: 7.7

12th Grade

S. D. Public School, East Patel Nagar, New Delhi

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Republic of Memers: A web-app (08/2020 - 08/2020) 🗹

 I created this application in over one night it includes database management.

Detection of COVID-19 by X-rays using Machine Learning And Deep Learning Models (05/2020 - 06/2020) ☑

 Research Paper selected and published by International Conference on Computing, Communication and Cyber Security (IC4S-2020)

Sell That Out (06/2020) 🗗

 A quicker and Olx like web Application that can be used to Buy & Sell Old products for college students.

Code Link- https://github.com/creatorpiyush/slot machine

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Development Intern

Catsflare

11/2020 - Present

Worked As a Teaching Assistant Coding-Blocks

01/2020 - 04/2020

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

Participated in IC4S-2020 conference for Machine Learning and paper successfully published (10/2020 - 10/2020) ☑

Detection of COVID-19 by X-rays using Machine Learning And Deep Learning Models

CERTIFICATES

Google Hash-Code 2020 (02/2020) 🗹

Scored "4197th" position world-wide(in 10 Million teams)

GitHub - HACK ON hackathon 🗹

IC4S-2020 conference for Machine Learning

Problem Solving (Advanced) Certificate

Building Web Apps with REACT JS - Coding Blocks

Web Development with Node.js - Coding Blocks

Crux-Java & Data Structures - Coding Blocks

LANGUAGES



INTERESTS

